kimkim.com 2017-02-15

# Privacy Policy | kimkim

###### kimkim, Inc.

#### Privacy Policy

Last Updated: January 15, 2016

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by kimkim, Inc. (“ ** _kimkim_** ,” “ ** _we_** ,” “ ** _us_** ” or “ ** _our_** ”) when you access or use our website, mobile application and other online products and services (collectively, our “ ** _Services_** ”) or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will revise the “Last Updated” date above and attempt to provide additional notice by providing information through our Services. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access or use our Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

###### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

**Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. The types of information we may collect include:

  * **Account Information** , such as your name, email address, password, profile photo, postal address, phone number, bio and any other information you choose to provide;
  * **Travel Information** , such as your travel history (including countries you have visited and the frequency of your visits) and your future travel plans; 
  * **Transaction Information** , such as the products or services you purchase or offer for sale through our Services. We may also collect and store limited payment information from you, such as payment card type and expiration date and the last four digits of your payment card number; however, we do not collect or store full payment card numbers and all transactions are processed by our third party payment processor. If you offer products or services for sale through our Services, we will also collect your bank account information;
  * **Information About Others** , such as the names, email addresses and other information and preference of your travel companions or individuals you invite to use our Services; and
  * **Other Information You Choose to Provide** , such as when you participate in a survey, contest, promotion, quiz or interactive area of the Services, request technical or customer support, communicate with us via third-party social media services or otherwise communicate with us.

**Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services**

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

  * **Log Information:** We collect log information about your access to and use of our Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * **Device Information:** We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.
  * **Location Information:** With your consent (e.g. if you permit your mobile device to send us your latitude and longitude), we will collect location information when you access or use our Service and, if permitted by your device settings, in the “background” (i.e. at times when you are not directly using the Services). For more details, please see "Your Choices" below.
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies, web beacons, web storage and device identifiers. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

**Information We Collect from Other Sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including identity verification services, credit bureaus and publicly available sources. If you create or log into your account through a social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and email address, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site.

###### USE OF INFORMATION

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information;
  * Manage your account and send you related information, including confirmations, updates, technical notices, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by kimkim and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services; 
  * Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of kimkim and others;
  * Personalize and improve our Services and provide advertisements, content and features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with a better experience; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

kimkim is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using our Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

###### SHARING OF INFORMATION

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * When you create a profile, participate in the interactive areas of our Services or interact with us on third-party social media sites, certain information that you provide may be displayed publicly, such as your name, profile photo, travel history and other information you choose to provide;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, rule, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property or safety of kimkim or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
  * Between and among kimkim and any current or future parent, subsidiary and/or affiliated company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf and provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Services and other applications and websites, including your IP address, web browser, device type, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other applications and websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

We may also work with third-party social media sites, such as Facebook, to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign, unless you notify us that you prefer not to have information about you used in this way. For more information about how you can opt out of customized campaigns, please see “Your Choices” below.

###### YOUR CHOICES

**Account Information**

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging in to your account and editing your information. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email team@kimkim.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

**Cookies and Web Storage**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies and web storage by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject cookies and web storage. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies or web storage, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. 

**Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or SMS messagesfrom kimkim by following the instructions in those emails or messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations

**Push Notifications**

With your consent, we may send promotional and non-promotional push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device or within our mobile applications.

###### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [team@kimkim.com](mailto:team@kimkim.com)
